A Guide to the Henry H. Douglas Collection, 1861-1978
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 2: Negatives
  - Sub-series 2-2: Echoes of History, 1968-1976
    - Sudley Church Hospital, Prince William County, Va., ca. 1861 (v. 5, no. 2,, p. 32), Undated (Box 2)
    - Battery Rodgers, Alexandria, Va./Sudley United Methodist Church, Prince William County, Va. (v. 5, no. 2, p. 33 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Battery Rodgers, Alexandria, va. (v. 5, no. 2, p. 34), Undated (Box 2)
    - Rebecca Crowley House, Mullica River near Green Bank, Cape May, NJ (v. 5, no. 3, p. 39), Undated (Box 2)
    - Map of Pine Barrens in southern NJ/ Pine Barrens road in southern NJ (v. 5, no. 3, p. 41 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Early Roads in Harrisville, NJ, area/ Ruins of Harrisville/ Grist Mill ruins/ Paper Mill Ruins (v. 5, no. 3, p. 42 [4 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Houses on Main Street, Batsto, NJ ca. 1905 (v. 5, no. 3, p. 44), Undated (Box 2)
    - J. Coleman with two story double house, Batsto, NJ, ca. 1905 (v. 5, no. 3, p. 45), Undated (Box 2)
    - Map of Urban Development NJ Shore Region (v. 5, no. 3, p. 46), Undated (Box 2)
    - View at Sea Grove House, Cape May Point, NJ (v. 5, no. 3, p. 47), Undated (Box 2)
    - Chalfonte, Cape May, NJ (v. 5, no. 3, p. 48), Undated (Box 2)
    - Ross Bathing House, Ocean Grove, NJ (v. 5, no. 3, p. 48), Undated (Box 2)
    - Drawbridge at Green Bank, Cape May, NJ (v. 5, no. 3, p. 51), Undated (Box 2)
    - Manassas Gap Railroad, unfinished Independent Line over Bull Run (v. 5, no. 4, p. 53), 1975 November (Box 2)
    - Manassas Gap Railroad, old roadbed on Royce Street, Annandale, Va. (v. 5, no. 4, p, 54), Undated (Box 2)
    - Manassas Gap Railroad, roadbed near Mill Creek Road west of Beltway (v. 5, no. 4, p. 55), Undated (Box 2)
    - Manassas Gap Railroad, stone abutment over Cub Run (v. 5, no. 4, p. 56), 1975 March (Box 2)
    - Manassas Gap Railroad, stonework for Bull Run bridge/ Mary Barrett standing on old roadbed near Sudley Church (v. 5, no. 3, p. 57 [2 negatives]), 1974 November, 1975 January (Box 2)
    - Groveton Memorial, adjacent to Manassas Gap Railroad roadbed/Old roadbed crossing Cain Branch (v. 5, no. 3, p. 58 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Manassas Gap Railroad proposed Dead Run crossing near Dulles Airport (v. 5, no. 3, p. 59), 1974 March (Box 2)
    - Swartz Mill, Shenandoah County, Va. Images (v. 5, no. 4, p. 60 [4 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Fairfax County weights and measures (v. 5, no. 4, p. 61), Undated (Box 2)
    - Beverley Mill (v. 5, no. 4, p. 63), Undated (Box 2)
    - Broad Run Station and Broad Run/ exterior of Station/Elizabeth Bloxton inside the Station (v. 5, no. 4, p. 64 [3 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Broad Run Station/ Recuperation Camp west of Thoroughfare Gap, adjacent to the Station, Fauquier County,, Va. (v. 5, no. 4, p. 65 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Catharpin, Prince William County, Va., Post Office ca. 1920's/ Manassas Gap Railroad steam locomotive ca. 1905 (v. 5, no. 4, p. 66 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Catharpin, Va. Post Office and Store ca. 1938/ Store ca. 1971 (v. 5. no. 4, p. 67 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - E. N. Pattie store, Catharpin, VA., 1912 (v. 5, no. 4., p. 68), Undated (Box 2)
    - Catharpin School, ca.1913-1920/ Catharpin School 1971 (v. 5, no. 4, p. 69 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Map of Catharpin. Va. (v. 5, no. 4, p. 70), Undated (Box 2)
    - Peoples National Bank Building, Leesburg, Va. (?) (v. 5, no. 4, p. 71), Undated (Box 2)
    - Making wooden shingles/ Laying shingles (v. 6, no. 1, p. 7 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Van Ness "Barracks", Towaco, NJ/ Close up view of the iron pins supporting the roof (v. 6. no. 1, p. 9 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Himmsel Farm log barn, DuBois County, IN (v. 6, no. 1, p. 12), Undated (Box 2)
    - Intercourse, Lancaster County, Pa., street scene (v. 6, no. 2, p. 17), Undated (Box 2)
    - Ephrata Cloister Graveyard, Ephrata, Pa. (v. 6, no. 2, p. 18), Undated (Box 2)
    - Plow Tavern and the Gates House, York, Pa. (v. 6, no. 2, p. 19), Undated (Box 2)
    - Cherry Hill, Falls Church, Va. ca. 1874/ Repair of barn ca. 1975 (v. 6, no. 2, p. 20 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Birch House, Falls Church, Va. (v. 6, no. 2, p. 21), 1974 (Box 2)
    - Woodley Lane Farms Milk Bottle, Montgomery County, Md. (v. 6, no. 2, p. 25), Undated (Box 2)
    - Norfolk & Western station, Abingdon, Va. (v. 6. no. 3, p. 33), 1974 November (Box 2)
    - Belmont Hotel, Abingdon, Va. (v. 6, no. 3, p. 35), Undated (Box 2)
    - "The Virginia Creeper" sign, Abingdon, Va./ Locomotive (v. 6, no. 3, p. 36 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Norfolk & Western train at Creek Water Junction, along New River/ Train at Green Cove, unattributed, O. Winston Link photo, 1956 (v. 6. no. 3, p. 38 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Water tank at West Jefferson, NC, ca. 1975/ Old Caboose at Todd, NC ca. 1975 (v. 6, no. 3, p. 39 [2 negatives]), 1975 (Box 2)
    - John Nelson Follin ca 1863/ Follin House, 704 Walker Road near Colvin Run (v. 6, no. 3, p. 41 [2 negatives]), 1976 (Box 2)
    - Proud Cabin in the Woods (v. 6, no. 3, p. 48), Undated (Box 2)
    - Drawing of Lock at Great Falls, Va. (v. 6, no. 4, p. 49), Undated (Box 2)
    - Great Seal of the Potowmack Company (v. 6, no. 4, p. 52), Undated (Box 2)
    - Union Arch, Washington Aqueduct over Cabin John Creek Valley (v. 6, no. 4, p. 53), 1975 (Box 2)
    - Northern Wisconsin Farmstead (v. 6, no. 4, p. 55), Undated (Box 2)
    - Nels Wickstrom pioneer homestead, Florence County, WI/ Rural Finnish log sauna (v. 6, no. 4, p. 56 [2 negatives]), Undated (Box 2)
    - Stovewood Barn, Wisconsin (v. 6, no. 4, p. 57), Undated (Box 2)
    - Map of Bloom's Farm, Manassas, Va. (v. 6., no. 4, p. 60), Undated (Box 2)
    - Bloom's Farmhouse, ca. 1976 (v. 6, no. 3, p. 61), Undated (Box 2)
    - Map of Watergate of Alexandria Development (v. 6, no. 4, p. 62), Undated (Box 2)
    - Granite Boulder, oversized from Minor Granite Quarry (v. 6, no. 4, p. 63), Undated (Box 2)
    - Mt. Pleasant (v. 2, no. 6, p. 73), Undated (Box 2)
    - Old Mills of Virginia, 1931. (v. 3, no. 5, p. 73), Undated (Box 2)
    - Old Mills of Virginia, 1931. (v. 3, no. 5, p. 73), Undated (Box 2)
    - Camp Alger Headquarters(v. 4, no. 5, p. 75), Undated (Box 2)
    - Battle of Groveton marker [includes photographs], 1975 (Box 2)
  - Sub-series 2-3: Falls Church Historical News and Notes, 1967-1973
    - I.O.O.F. Hall, (built 1891), Falls Church (v. 1, no. 1., p. 1), 1970 April (Box 3)
    - Route 7 looking west (v. 1, no. 1, p. 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Mankin store and house with post office (built 1895) at right, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 1, p. 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Casilear House and Farm, 502 Walden Court, Falls Church, built circa 1890, side view of house (v. 1, no. 1, p. 4) (1 of 3), 1969 April (Box 3)
    - adobe house, 408 Lincoln Avenue, Falls Church, near Casilear House (v. 1, no. 1, p. 4) (2 of 3), 1969 April (Box 3)
    - Tallwood, Falls Church, built 1870s (v. 1, no. 1, p. 4) (3 of 3), 1969 April (Box 3)
    - Brown's Store and house while still used as a residence (v. 1, no. 1, p. 5) (1 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Hugh R. Brown (left) and his father, Horace E. Brown, Sr., in front of Brown's store, 1949. (v. 1, no. 1, p. 5) (2 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Brown's Store shortly before razing, 1959. (v. 1, no. 1, p. 5) (3 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Cherry Hill, 312 Park Avenue, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 1, p. 6), Undated (Box 3)
    - Washington & Old Dominion East Falls Church Station (v. 1., no. 1, p. 7), 1970 February (Box 3)
    - East Falls Church Railway Station (drawing from 1920's photo) (v. 1, no. 2, p. 1), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Antrim", 1311 Chestnut Street, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 2, p. 2), 1970 February (Box 3)
    - Cherry Hill barn corn crib, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 2, p. 3) (1 of 2), 1967 December (Box 3)
    - "Cherry Hill", home of Riley family from 1873 to 1968 (v. 1, no. 2, p. 3) (2 of 2), 1969 February (Box 3)
    - "Highland View", 7225 Leesburg Pike, built 1870 (v. 1, no. 2, p. 4) (1 of 2), 1970 February (Box 3)
    - "Highland View", architectural detail (v. 1, no. 2, p. 4) (2 of 2), 1970 February (Box 3)
    - Peach Grove Stock Farm, ad in 1906 Fairfax County Directory (v. 1, no. 2, p. 5) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - W.G. Shephard home and store, and the Washington, Arlington and Falls Church Trolley Station, 1922 (v. 1, no. 2, p. 5) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Royal Lodge, " 6704 Haycock Road, Falls Church, October 1941. (v. 1, no. 2, p. 7), Undated (Box 3)
    - The Falls Church from north side (v. 1, no. 2, p. 9), 1967 October (Box 3)
    - Columbia Baptist Church at North Washington and West Columbia Streets, ca. 1910. (v. 1, no. 2, p. 11) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Columbia Baptist Church 1909 stone building being demolished (v. 1, no. 2, p. 11) (2 of 2), 1968 March (Box 3)
    - Falls Church Railway Station #2 (v. 1, no. 2, p. 12) (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 3)
    - Falls Church Railway Station #3 (sketch) (v. 1, no. 2, p. 12) 2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Memorial Day parade passes in front of Edmonds house, 133 East Broad Street, Falls Church, William Fitzhugh Edmonds, 1956. (v. 1, no. 3, p. 1) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Mr. and Mrs. William Fitzhugh Edmonds, ca. 1940. (v. 1, no. 3, p. 1) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Windmill at "Woodbrook", 1011 Fowler St., Falls Church (v. 1, no. 3, p. 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Cline house (1919-1963), 351 North Washington St., Falls Church, ca. 1920s. (v. 1, no. 3, p. 4), Undated (Box 3)
    - Rollins house, 109 East Columbia St., Falls Church, built circa 1890 (v. 1, no. 3, p. 5), Undated (Box 3)
    - Back: Henry Redfield "Spin" Thompson, Virginia and Mrs. Elizabeth Anne and John Ballard; Front: George Sidney and Henry Franklin, ca. 1922. (v. 1, no. 3, p. 6), Undated (Box 3)
    - Drawing illustrating bicycle designed by "Spin" Thompson for use on W&OD Railroad, signed by Andy Davis (v. 1, no. 3, p. 7), Undated (Box 3)
    - Original home of Jacob Belz, Falls Church, built 1921 (v. 1, no. 3, p. 8), Undated (Box 3)
    - Left: Belz home, 1010 Tuckahoe St., Falls Church, remodeled 1929. Center: Brick home of Mr. and Mrs. Edwin P. White (Dorothea Belz). Operated as a school 1935-1970. Right: White houses built circa 1941. (v. 1, no. 3, p. 8), Undated (Box 3)
    - Dr. Thomas Melville Talbott, May 7, 1925. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 1) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Painting of Mrs. Henry J. Morgan (nee Harriett Hogan), painted by Mr. Morgan about 1876. Child, Jack, died shortly after picture was made. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 1) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Dr. Talbott, Philip M. Talbott, and Mrs. Talbott, Falls Church, 1897. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Dr. Talbott and daughter Kathleen, with his second Model T during World War I (v. 1, no. 4, p. 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Talbott house on McKinley Street, Falls Church, November 1927. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 4), Undated (Box 3)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Talbott at their son Philip's 6897 Washington Boulevard house, May 1937. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 5), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Cloverdale", drawing of house, Haycock Road, Falls Church, built by Rev. Robert M. Nourse probably in 1880s; subsequently owned by Mr. and Mrs. Edmund Howard Flagg and Mr. and Mrs. Chas. Taylor. Site of surface spring. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 6) (1 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Spring house at Birch house, 312 East Broad Street, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 4, p. 6) (2 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Spring house in Falls Hill, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 4, p. 6) (3 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Well house at Perry home at top of Woodland Drive near Highpoint Pool; deepest private well in Falls Church (205 ft) (v. 1, no. 4, p. 7) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Water tower at 201 North West Street, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 4, p. 7) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Water tower at Hollywood Farm on Route 7 across from George Mason High School (v. 1, no. 4, p. 8) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Windmill at "Woodbrook", 1011 Fowler St., "last remaining windmill in Falls Church" (v. 1, no. 4, p. 8), Undated (Box 3)
    - Roberts house, 409 South West Street, Falls Church (built 1867 by Milton S. Roberts) (v. 1, no. 4, p. 9), 1968 April (Box 3)
    - Roberts house, Milton S. Roberts and Miss Carrie Parker, ca. 1918. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 10) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Ad for "Golden Rule Poultry Farm", Falls Church, owned by Milton E. Roberts (v. 1, no. 4, p. 10) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Milton E. and Fannie Roberts in front parlor, 409 S. West St., Falls Church, ca. 1955. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 11), Undated (Box 3)
    - Judge Joseph S. Riley, the patriarch of Cherry Hill, ca. 1875. (v. 1, no. 5, p. 1), Undated (Box 3)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Harry Fellows and daughter Virginia in the front yard of their new home on Brown Avenue, Falls Church, 1902. (v. 1, no. 5, p. 3) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Fellows house (west side), 6404 North Washington Boulevard, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 5, p. 3) (2 of 2), 1971 August 1 (Box 3)
    - Pickering Dodge house, 6763 26th Street North in East Falls Church, built 1899 (v. 1, no. 5, p. 4), 1970 February (Box 3)
    - City water tank behind the State Theater near the center of Falls Church (1st tank built in Falls Church) (v. 1, no. 5, p. 5), Undated (Box 3)
    - The two water tanks at Falls Hill, located at back of Hollywood Farm just east of Flagg house (v. 1, no. 5, p. 6) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - 420 N. Washington Street (now demolished) (v. 1, no. 5, p. 6) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Drawing of Clover house as it looked on its orignal site, by Andrew Davis (v. 1, no. 5, p. 7) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Dulin Methodist Church, Falls Church, 1905. (v. 1, no. 5, p. 7) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Dulin Methodist Church and rectory, 1905. (v. 1, no. 5, p. 8), Undated (Box 3)
    - St. James Catholic Church (Spring Street entrance), Falls Church (v. 1, no. 5, p. 9), 1970 November (Box 3)
    - Hollywood Farm house (east side), Falls Church (v. 1, no. 5, p. 11) (1 of 3), 1971 August 8 (Box 3)
    - Rixey house, 7257 Lee Highway, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 5, p. 11) (2 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Rixey house in earlier form, 1861. (v. 1, no. 5, p. 11) (3 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Jefferson Institute (completed 1886), 300 block East Broad Street, Falls Church, ca 1891. (v. 1, no. 5, p. 12) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - 271 N. Washington Street, Falls Church (since demolished) (v. 1, no. 5, p. 12) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Caricature of George Louis Erwin (1859-1938) by unknown artist (v. 1, no. 6, p. 1), Undated (Box 3)
    - Maynard Erwin in 1920 at age 16 (v. 1, no. 6, p. 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - George Louis Erwin, ca 1900. (v. 1, no. 6, p. 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Ware's Drug Store, East Falls Church, at left is Mrs. John P. Stoddard, at right is Mrs. John Taylor, ca 1930. (v. 1, no. 6, p. 5) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Maple Shade, " built 1899 by Jonas Unverzagt (v. 1, no. 6, p. 5) (2 of 2), 1970 April (Box 3)
    - Restored well house, Cherry Hill, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 6, p. 7) (1 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Corn crib before restoration, Cherry Hill, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 6, p. 7) (2 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Restored corn crib, Cherry Hill, Falls Church (v. 1, no. 6, p. 7) (3 of 3), 1971 November (Box 3)
    - Turner/Lee/Rees House, 509 West Broad Street (showing seldom-seen three story side) (v. 1, no. 6, p. 10), 1969 April (Box 3)
    - "Chestnut Grove", home of Ada Walker (1875-1969), 2124 Great Falls Street, Falls Church (v. 2, no. 1, p. 4), Undated (Box 3)
    - James Isaac Brown, principal of Jefferson School, Falls Church, ca 1870s. (v. 2, no. 1, p. 6), Undated (Box 3)
    - Jefferson School (steps and porticos) (v. 2, no. 1, p. 7), Undated (Box 3)
    - Taylor home, 419 W. Broad Street, Falls Church (v. 2, no. 1, p. 8) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Ada Walker in her carriage in the yard of the Walker home, 1914-1915. (v. 2, no. 1, p. 8) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Lee house, 505 W. Broad St., Falls Church, ca 1930. (v. 2, no. 1, p. 9), Undated (Box 3)
    - Mrs. Horace E. Brown (Sarah Augusta Rose) (v. 2, no. 1, p. 12) (1 of 2), 1969 September (Box 3)
    - East Falls Church during the Spanish American War, 1898. (v. 2, no. 1, p. 12) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Fannie May and Carroll V. Shreve on the lawn of the Ellison house, 928 West Broad Street, Falls Church, 1946. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 13), Undated (Box 3)
    - Ellison house, 928 West Broad St., Falls Church, November 1967. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 14) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Ellison house, 928 West Broad St., Falls Church, March 1955. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 14) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Lawton House, built in the 1850s by C.H. Buxton; another photo of the house was the frontispiece in A Virginia Village (1904) (v. 2, no. 2, p. 17), 1969 April (Box 3)
    - Wm. McElfresh Ellison home, 934 W. Broad St., Falls Church; See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 6, and Falls Church: By Fence and Fireside, figures 49 and 50 (v. 2, no. 2, p. 18), Undated (Box 3)
    - Brown's store, Falls Church, Three types of one horse carriages are shown. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 14; Falls Church: By Fence and Fireside, figure 6 (v. 2, no. 2, p. 19) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Brown's Hardware, Falls Church, just prior to demolition. 1959. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 19) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Erwin house, 300 West Great Falls Street, Falls Church, built about 1890 by George Louis Erwin. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 15. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 20), 1969 March (Box 3)
    - Dr. George B. Fadeley home, built about 1890, Falls Church. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 11. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 21), 1971 March (Box 3)
    - Major M.S. Hopkins home, Falls Church. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 18. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 22), Undated (Box 3)
    - 251 North Washington St., Falls Church. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 21. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 23), Undated (Box 3)
    - Crossman house, Falls Church. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 24. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 24) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Rollins house, 109 East Columbia St., Falls Church, built circa 1890. See A Virginia Village (1904), p. 32. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 24) (2 of 2), 1970 November (Box 3)
    - 914 West Broad St., Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 2, p. 27), 1967 November (Box 3)
    - The Falls Church, built 1769, with Ball-Dulany plot in foreground. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 29), Undated (Box 3)
    - Bailey plot, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 32) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Bailey gravestones, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 32) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Simon Sommers (Revolutionary War soldier) gravestone, The Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 34), Undated (Box 3)
    - John Carolin gravestone, oldest at The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 35), Undated (Box 3)
    - Rev. George Somerville gravestone, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 36), Undated (Box 3)
    - Julien Mederic Desrochers and wife, Jennie Mitchell Alexander, gravestone, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 37), Undated (Box 3)
    - Hodgkin family plot, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 38) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Julian Fitzhugh Slade gravestone, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 38) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Funeral of James Maynadier Mason III, July 12, 1969, Rev. J. Hodge Alves officiating, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 39) (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 3)
    - Gravestone of James M. Mason III (1892-1969), the Falls Church, last direct descendant of George Mason living in this area (v. 2, no. 3, p. 39) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Hog butchering, 1942. Left to right: Joe Jeffries, unidentified, Dr. Oscar Kiessling, Dave Leonard. Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 41), Undated (Box 3)
    - "The meat crop", 1938. The poultry house is in the background. Kiessling farm, Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 42) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Frozen stiff", 1938. Dr. Oscar Kiessling transports a pig to the "deep freeze" in the barn. Kiessling farm, Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 42) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Rapid transit", horse-drawn sled, 1938. Dr. Oscar Kiessling, Peter Kiessling, Julie Kiessling, Joe Jeffries. Kiessling farm, Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 43) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Mass transportation", 1954. Dr. Alice Kiessling in rear of wagon, Joe Jeffries driving. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 43) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Harvest time at the Kiesslings, 1956. Dr. Alice Kiessling, Julie Kiessling, Schatze, Peter Kiessling, Dr. Oscar Kiessling. Kiessling farm, Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 44), Undated (Box 3)
    - Tree harvest, 1945. Kiessling farm, Falls Church. (v. 2, no. 3, p. 46), Undated (Box 3)
    - Gravestone of Maggie H. Rawlings (died 1881), first recorded non-member to be interred in the church yard of The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 3, p. 50), 1972 (Box 3)
    - 210 East Fairfax Street, Falls Church, about 1916. Birthplace of Olive Harmon Robey. (v. 2, no. 4, p. 55) (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Harmon's blacksmith shop, East Fairfax Street, Falls Church. Mr. Harmon and Henry Simms examine a wheel in need of repair. ca 1942. (v. 2, no. 4, p. 55) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - Abbott Store, Falls Church, March 1958. (v. 2, no. 4, p. 56), Undated (Box 3)
    - Harmon's blacksmith shop, East Fairfax Street, Falls Church, probably taken before WWI. (v. 2, no. 4, p. 58), Undated (Box 3)
    - Gravestone of Nicholas Darne (at The Falls Church), a Captain in the War of 1812 and descendant of Henry Darne who built the Vestry House in 1766 (v. 2, no. 4, p. 61), Undated (Box 3)
    - Charles Alexander Stewart house, west end of Brown Avenue, Falls Church. ca 1900. (v. 2, no. 4, p. 69) (1 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Charles Alexander Stewart house, on what is now North Washington Boulevard, Falls Church (v. 2, no. 4, p. 69) (2 of 3), 1970 February (Box 3)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Charles Alexander Stewart on the porch of their home in the late 1930's, Falls Church (v. 2, no. 4 p. 69) (3 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Four "dornick" stones on west side of The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 4, p. 70) (1 of 2), 1973 February (Box 3)
    - "Dornick" stone at The Falls Church. Inscription dated 1786 (v. 2, no. 4, p. 70) (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Dornick" stone at The Falls Church. Inscribed 1776 (v. 2, no. 4, p. 71) (1 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Dornick" stone at The Falls Church. Inscribed 1786 (v. 2, no. 4, p. 71) (2 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Dornick" stone at The Falls Church. No inscription (v. 2, no. 4, p. 71) (3 of 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Harold J. Spelman (left) with The Rev. Joel Pugh holding 1754 Folio edition of Book of Common Prayer, The Falls Church (v. 2, no. 4, p. 72), Undated (Box 3)
    - The Creeks of Falls Church, Left, Tripp's Run flows into Lake Barcroft; Right, Four Mile Run follows the W&OD railroad roadbed to Alexandria (v. 1, no. 2, p. 6), Undated (Box 3)
    - Milton E. Roberts and his poultry plant (in Falls Church) about 1940. At the top of the hill the building with the cupola was the earliest barn. The house is at upper left. (v. 1, no. 4, p. 10), Undated (Box 3)
    - Joe Jeffries (who worked for the Kiessling family on their farm in Falls Church) about 1941, in butler's coat ready to serve dinner (v. 2, no. 3, p. 44), Undated (Box 3)
    - "Woodbrook", 1011 Fowler Street, Falls Church, "The only remaining windmill in Falls Church, Va., is shown here in the yard of Woodbrook, the home of Mr. and Mrs. Arthur S. Kaye. It can hardly be seen except in winter. The house was probably built about 1890, and was the home of the Hertz family from 1928 to 1960. The drawing is by Carolyne Grosse." (v. 1, no. 3, p. 3), Undated (Box 3)
    - Ada Walker (1875-1969) and her mother, Harriett (Watkins) Walker, in 1925 (v. 2, no. 1, p. 3), Undated (Box 3)